Guide to the Derrick A. Bell, Jr. Papers MC.138
New York University Archives
- SERIES III: SUBJECT FILES, A-Y, 1970-1985 (Boxes 30-49)
  - Edmonds & Cheng Memorial fund, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Education/Instruccion, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Emory University Law School, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Emory University Law School, 1981-1984 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Emory Law Journal, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Emory Minority Grade Study, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Employment, student, undated (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Employment, student, undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Encyclopedia of Southern History, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275134
  - Esquire, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Evers, Medgar (funeral), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Ewald Professor (Univ. Virginia Law School, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "F" subjects, 1975-1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "F" (students), 1971-1979 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - First Year, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Florida State Law Exchange, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Freedom House, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - "G" subjects, 1970-1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Grand Jury problems, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Guinier, Carol Lani RESTRICTED, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Gulf Oil, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - "H" subjects, 1974-1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Hate mail, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - HEW Report, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - HEW, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - HEW, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - HEW, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Higginbotham book project, 1972-1977 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Hilton Head conference, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Hollis Presbyterian Church Forum, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution & Peace, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Hospitals, Initiation of Enforcement proceedings, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Howard Law School, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Howard Law School, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Howard University, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Harvard University - Afro Studies Dept., 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275142
  - Harvard University - Alumni, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University - Black Alumni Assn., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Black Law Students Assn., 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University - Black Law Students Assn., 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Testimonial Dinner, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University - Black Alumni/Career Day, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University - Black Law Students Assn., 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Harvard University - BLSA Testimonial Dinner, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University - Black Faculty and Administrators, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Harvard University - Black Admissions, 1971-1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Harvard University - Black Problems, 1971-1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Harvard University - General Counsel's Office, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, Bell v. Reedman, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Record, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Review, 1972-1977 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law Review - Supreme Court Issue, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Harvard University - Faculty File, Jan 1970-Aug 1970 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Harvard University - Memos, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Harvard University - Harvard Law School, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Harvard Law School Memoranda, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Harvard Law School Teaching, Sep 1978 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Harvard Law School, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Harvard Law School, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Harvard Law School Faculty Memos, Directory, undated (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Harvard Law School Advisees, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Harvard Law Minority Law School Admits, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Harvard Law School (includes boycott materials), 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275159
  - Harvard Law School, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - The Outlaw, vol. 1 no. 6 - Harvard Law School and Boston University Law School joint publication, 1971 (Box Shared University Archives 001)
  - Harvard Legal Assistance Program, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Medical School Minority Admissions, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Racial Issues Study Group, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Harvard-Radcliffe Afro-American Cultural Center, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Univ. Divinity School, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Univ. Hall - Protest, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - "I" subjects, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Law School, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Institute of the Black world, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Research on Poverty, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Research on Poverty, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - "J" subjects, 1976-1984 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Jews - Jewish Organizations, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Job offers, 1971-1977 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Judging Process, the, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Judicial Program, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Judicial Selection Committee, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Juris Doctor article, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - "K" subjects, 1972-1985 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Katz, Stanley - issue, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - KEDS General Assistance Center - Kent State, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Kennedy Institute of Politics, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Kilson Protest, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275167
  - King, Martin Luther, 1973-1985 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "L" subjects, 1970-1981 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Law - Divinity Lecture, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Law and Education Center, 1960-1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Law Review, Table of Contents, 1972-1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Law School Admission, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Law School Admission Council, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - LSAT, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Law and Social Change - Africa (articles), undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - LANAC/Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, 1982-1985 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - LANAC/Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, Lane County, Oregon, 1982-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lawyers Against Apartheid, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Lawrence, Charles, 1974-1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Law Review, correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Legal Defense Fund, 1970-1984 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Legal Education, 1960-1974 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Legal Education, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Legal Methods, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Legal Services Corp., 1975-1978 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Legal Services History, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Lehman, Herbert, Educational Fund, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Los Angeles School Board Case, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - "M", 1977-1981 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275175
  - MacDowell Colony, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - MARC Conference, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Mass. Associations, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Mass. Assn. Against Discrimination, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - McCann Education Class, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Church Daily Prayers, 1976-1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Minority Directory, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Minority Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Minority Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Minority Directory, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Minority Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Minority Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Minority Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Minority Faculty, bibliographies and resumes, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Minority faculty, resumes, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Minority faculty, resumes, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Minority faculty, questionnaires, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Minority faculty, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Minority group, 1974-1979 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Minority Law Teachers Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275183
  - Minority (student) opportunities, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1981-1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1981-1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1980-1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Minority Recommendations, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Minority Tenure Problems RESTRICTED, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Minority Tenure Problems RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Morse, Wayne, historical park, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Multi-culture Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Murphy Amendment (OEO), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - "N" subjects, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - NAACP, 1982-1985 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - NAACP Legal Defense/Education Fund, 1960-1965 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - NAACP Legal Defense/Education Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - NAACP Legal Defense/Education Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund, 1970- 1973 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund - Miscellaneous, 1956-1966 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - NAACP v. ITT Corp., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - National Bar Association, 1974-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275191
  - National Bar Association, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - National Bar Conventions, 1971, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - National Bar Foundation, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination In Housing, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination In Housing, 1971-1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination In Housing, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination In Housing, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination In Housing, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1973-1984 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1981-1984 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - National Conference on Testing in Education and Employment, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275209
  - National Council for Effective Schools, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - National Education Assn., 1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - NEH Summer Seminar, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - NEH Application Review "The Amistad Affair", 1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - NEH Seminar (Harvard), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - NEH Seminar (Harvard), 1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - National Institute of Education - "Toward Effective Desegregated Schools", 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - National Lawyers Guild (New York Chapter), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - NLADA Leadership Project - Legal Services Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - National Policy Conference on Education For Blacks, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - National Program Underwriting (Pittsburgh), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - National Reporter on Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility, 1982-1984 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Negro History Bulletin, 1953-1958 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Negro History Documents, 1940s-1950s (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Newman, John, Judge, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - New Birth Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - New York Public Library, Constitution Exhibit, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - New York University - Institute of Judicial Administration, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - New York University - lecture, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - New York University - employment considerations, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - New York University Conference - Clark, Leroy, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - NCOSTA Conference, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - North Carolina Central University, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - North Mississippi Rural Legal Services, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - "O" subjects, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275217
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - OE Compliance, 1964-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Oregon Black Attorneys, 1982-1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Oregon Law Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Law Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Univ. Oregon Law School, correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Oregon Law School, ABA/AALS, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Oregon Law School, study, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Oregon, Univ. Of, Board of Trustees, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "P" subjects, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Pan-African Liberation Committee, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Pass-Fail Grading, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1973-1977 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh NAACP, 1952-1957 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Plea Bargaining, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Portland Schools, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Portland State Univ. Black Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Practicing Institute for Lawyers, 1972-1979 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Practicing Institute for Lawyers, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Practicing Institute for Lawyers, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Prison Letters, 1972-1975 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Prisoners' Rights, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Program for Southern Legal Internships, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Progressive Labor Party, ca.1970 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Queens College Law School, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275225
  - "R" subjects, 1977-1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Race Relations Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Randolph, A. Philip, Institute (Oregon), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Ravenswood Schools, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Ravitch, Diane (desegregation), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - "Reading Is Yours to Keep", 1975 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - "Reading Is Yours to Keep", 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "Reading Is Yours to Keep", 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "Reading Is Yours to Keep", 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Referendum Research, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Referendum Research, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Research Project - Students from Minority Groups - Harvard Business School, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Resignation - Harvard University, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Resignation - University of Oregon, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Resignation - University of Oregon, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Resignation - University of Oregon, Support Letters, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Richardson, Henry, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Roxbury Multi-Service Center, 1969-1972 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Ruffin, George Lewis - Program, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - "S" subjects, 1976-1984 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275233
  - "S" student recommendations/evaluations, 1972-1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco Schools, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco Schools, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco public schools, 1975-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Schomburg Center/New York Public Library, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - School Desegregation, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - School Desegregation, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - School Desegregation, 1974-1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - School Desegregation Developments, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - School Desegregation/Encyclopedia of the American Constitution, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - School Desegregation - Legislation, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Schools Judicial Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Schools - poor performers, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Schwartz, Murray, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Sex discrimination, 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Shockley-Innis debate, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Shockley-Innis debate, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Slavery, 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Reginald H., fellowship, 1972-1975 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - SALT, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - School Desegregation, 1970s (Box 46, File 21)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275241
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - SALT - Society of American Law Teachers Awards, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - South Africa, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - South Africa - litigation, 1974-1976 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Southern California, Univ. Of, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Student correspondence, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Summer Employees, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - "T" subjects, 1972-1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275258
  - Tarrytown Conferences - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1981-1983 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Tarrytown Conferences - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1981-1983 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Tarrytown meeting, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Tarrytown conferences (binder), 1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Thurman, Howard, Educational Trust, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Thurman, Howard, Educational Trust, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Thurman, Howard, Educational Trust, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Thurman, Howard, Educational Trust, Planning Session, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Thurman, Howard, Tapes, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Teaching fellows, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Testing, 1962-1976 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Tillery, Tyrone (Oregon), 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "U" subjects, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Uhuru Sasa (Homer D. Clay), 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - United Parcel Service, 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Urban Service Corps (New Haven), 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - "V" subjects, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - "W", 1978-1982 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Washington, Univ. of, lectures, ca.1978 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Washington, Univ. of, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275266
  - Washington, Univ. of, Gellhorn resignation, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Washington, Univ. of, Jurisprudence Lecture Series, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Washington, Univ. of, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Washington, Univ. of, Visiting Professor, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty Cases, 1968-1975 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1968-1975 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1970-1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - White Supremacy Activity, reports of, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Preston, Ford Foundation Project, 1974-1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Preston, Ford Foundation Project, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Winston, Jim - case, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Writing opportunities, 1973-1979 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Yale Law Journal article, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Yale Law Journal article, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Yale Law Journal article, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Xerox XIP, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Yarmolinsky, Adam (school desegregation), 1977 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - "Your Schools" (S. Carolina AFSC), 1974 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Youth & Crime, 1974-1977 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- SERIES IV: COURSE MATERIALS, 1969-1988 (Boxes 50-59)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275274
  - Miscellaneous B, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Dallas Case, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous D, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - [Educational Issues], 1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Employment, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Employment Discrimination, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous E (Affirmative Action), 1970s (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous F (Affirmative Action), 1970s (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous G (Affirmative Action), 1970s (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous H, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Anti-busing, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Employment Discrimination class notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275282
  - Employment Discrimination class notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Employment Discrimination class notes, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Employment Discrimination, Exams, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Employment Discrimination, course, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Exams, hypothetical problems RESTRICTED, 1970-1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - First-Year writing elective, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Florida State University RESTRICTED, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Seminar, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Grades, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Law and Slavery, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Law, Lawyers and Social Change, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Law and Society, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Race, correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Race, Racism, and American Law, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - "Race, Racism..." (Black Awakening in Capitalist America by Robert L. Allen, 1970) (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Race, Racism, and American Law, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Race, Racism, and American Law - "Slavery Law and Current Race Problems", 1972 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Race, Racism, and American Law, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Race, Racism, and American Law, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - "Race, Racism, and American Law, 1865 to present" by Randall J. Kennedy, syllabus and course materials, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - "Race, Racism, and American Law, 1865 to present" by Randall J. Kennedy, syllabus and course materials, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Barcode:31142042275290
  - "Race, Racism, and American Law, 1865 to present" by Randall J. Kennedy, syllabus and course materials, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Race Relations (Univ. Cal./Berkeley), 1969 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Seminar Plan, Mar 1981 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Slavery course, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Slavery course, correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Small group class, 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Constitutional Law, class notes, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 8)